♪♪♪
♪ BABY I'M AMAZED AT THE WAY
YOU LOVE ME ALL THE TIME ♪
♪ AND MAYBE I'M AFRAID
OF THE WAY I LOVE YOU ♪
♪ MAYBE I'M AMAZED ♪
♪ AT THE THE WAY YOU
PULLED ME OUT OF TIME ♪
♪ AND HUNG ME ON A LINE ♪
♪ AND MAYBE I'M AMAZED AT
THE WAY I REALLY NEED YOU ♪
♪ BABY, I'M A MAN,
MAYBE I'M A LONELY MAN ♪
♪ WHO'S IN THE
MIDDLE OF SOMETHING ♪
♪ THAT HE DOESN'T
REALLY UNDERSTAND ♪
♪ BABY, I'M A MAN, MAYBE
YOU'RE THE ONLY WOMAN ♪
♪ WHO COULD EVER HELP ME ♪
♪ BABY, WON'T YOU HELP
ME TO UNDERSTAND ♪
♪ OOH, OOH ♪
♪♪♪
♪ BABY, I'M A MAN,
MAYBE I'M A LONELY MAN ♪
♪ WHO'S IN THE
MIDDLE OF SOMETHING ♪
♪ THAT HE DOESN'T
REALLY UNDERSTAND ♪
♪ BABY, I'M A MAN, MAYBE
YOU'RE THE ONLY WOMAN ♪
♪ WHO COULD EVER HELP ME ♪
♪ BABY, WON'T YOU HELP
ME TO UNDERSTAND ♪
♪ OOH, OOH ♪
♪ MAYBE I'M AMAZED AT THE WAY
YOU'RE WITH ME ALL THE TIME ♪
♪ AND MAYBE I'M AFRAID
OF THE WAY I LEAVE YOU ♪
♪ MAYBE I'M AMAZED AT THE WAY
YOU HELP ME SING MY SONG ♪
♪ RIGHT ME WHEN I'M WRONG ♪
♪ AND MAYBE I'M AMAZED AT
THE WAY I REALLY NEED YOU ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH ♪
♪ YEAH ♪
♪ OH, OH, OH, OH, OOH, OOH ♪
♪ YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, OOH, OOH ♪
[GUITAR SOLO]
♪♪♪